#### Contact

reza.shahnazar@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rezashahnazar (LinkedIn) t.me/techproductinline (Other)

### Top Skills

Myocardial Infarction
Electrocardiography (EKG)
Pulmonary Hypertension

#### Certifications

Cardiologist

**Medical Doctor** 

National Biology Olympiad Gold Medal

### **Publications**

Association between Nontraditional Risk Factors and Calculated 10-Year Risk of Atherosclerotic Cardiovascular Disease in a Large General Population: Based on the Pars Cohort Study

Classic Genetics

**Essentials of Biostatistics** 

Cranial nerve palsy prevalence and associated factors in patients with malignant otitis externa

Abstract 431: MaxSpliZer: A Tool To Predict Effects Of LDLR Splice Variants Based On The Maximum Entropy Model

# Reza Shahnazar

Product Marketing Manager @ Digikala.com | Al Product Engineer | Cardiologist, MD

Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

# Summary

With over 15 years of comprehensive work experience, including a dedicated focus on business analytics and product development for the past 7 years, I've had the privilege of contributing to various projects and initiatives. Currently, at Digikala, my role revolves around enhancing customer experience by bridging the gap between business needs and technical solutions. This involves aligning the Marketing and Product departments and overseeing the technical product management of an agile software engineering team responsible for crafting on-demand marketing web-pages, services, and tools. My interest lies in the human-centric convergence of business and technology, where I approach challenges with a result-oriented perspective.

# Experience

Digikala

2 years 8 months

Product Marketing Manager June 2024 - Present (8 months)

Product Marketing Supervisor October 2023 - June 2024 (9 months)

Data Science Supervisor
January 2023 - October 2023 (10 months)
Tehran, Iran

Senior Data Science Specialist June 2022 - January 2023 (8 months) Tehran, Iran

Tehran Heart Center
Cardiology Resident
September 2018 - December 2022 (4 years 4 months)

Page 1 of 4

Tehran, Iran

ZiDoctor

9 months

Chief Technology Officer September 2021 - May 2022 (9 months)

Tehran, Iran

Co-Founder September 2021 - May 2022 (9 months)

Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

Young Scholars Publication
Book Author
January 2010 - March 2022 (12 years 3 months)
Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

Essentials of Biostatistics - Descriptive Solutions for National Biology Olympiad Exams

sClass College
Business Owner
May 2018 - May 2021 (3 years 1 month)
Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

sClass College was an online platform providing students all over the country with high quality interactive online biology olympiad classes delivered by the best teachers handpicked for different topics. Having access to classes with professional teachers were limited to only a few large cities those years. The business model and the go to market strategy initially resulted in a great success according to acquisition rate in both students and teachers side; However, sClass College was decided to be stopped when online classes happened to be easily accessible individually through various platforms after COVID-19 and scaling the business seemed to be unnecessary.

National Organization for Development of Exceptional Talents (Sampad)
Biostatistics & Genetics Teacher

October 2009 - May 2020 (10 years 8 months)

Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

Talayiha Club Biology Olympiad Program Coordinator & Teacher

Page 2 of 4

#### January 2015 - March 2020 (5 years 3 months)

Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

Fatemi Publishing House Book Author

March 2013 - March 2020 (7 years 1 month)

Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

Classical Genetics, focused on preparation for Biology olympid exams. Published in 5 Editions with over 5000 copies sold.

Allameh Tabatabaei Complex of Cultural and Educational Biostatistics & Genetics Teacher March 2013 - March 2018 (5 years 1 month)

Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

Farzanegan 2 Tehran Biology Olympiad Program Director September 2013 - April 2017 (3 years 8 months)

Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

Farzanegan 1 Tehran
Biostatistics & Genetics Teacher
March 2014 - March 2017 (3 years 1 month)
Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

Tehran University of Medical Sciences General Medicine Intern March 2014 - March 2017 (3 years 1 month) Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

Allameh Helli school Biology Olympid Program Director September 2013 - August 2015 (2 years)

Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

Young Scholars Club 3 years 3 months

Summer School Director of National Biology Olympiad July 2010 - July 2012 (2 years 1 month)

Tehran, Iran

### National Biology Olympiad Committee Member August 2009 - May 2012 (2 years 10 months)

Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

Biochemistry Teacher June 2009 - May 2012 (3 years)

Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

National Biology Olympiad Exam Coordinator November 2009 - May 2011 (1 year 7 months)

Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

Scientific Program Director of International Biology Olympiad Preparation Camp

August 2009 - May 2011 (1 year 10 months)

Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

Summer School Lab Coordinator of National Biology Olympid May 2009 - August 2009 (4 months)

Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

### Education

Tehran University of Medical Sciences

Doctor of Medicine - MD, Cardiology · (September 2018 - October 2022)

Tehran University of Medical Sciences

Doctor of Medicine - MD, Medicine · (2009 - 2016)